** Baleda, Julianne Paulene A. **
** CMSC 100 Expectations **

	After experiencing the Exercise 2 of the course, I realized (again) that figuring out how to make something work a certain way and conceptualizing and designing are entirely different tasks. It is not a good idea to perform both on the fly, at least for me. I struggled with organizing both my thoughts and the elements in the HTML page. Only when I sat down to draw how I wanted the page to look like first was I able to tackle coding those information and elements on my page. With that, the topics in CMSC 100 beyond HTML and CSS (and some JavaScript basics) will be entirely new to me. With the help of our kind instructor, I hope to finish the course with a newfound appreciation and deeper understanding of web programming.

